處理。
議員議案呢次會議一共係有五項議員議案，第一及第二項。
係根據以適意及通則條例動議有關延展附屬法例修訂期限嘅議議決議案。
第一項議案延展於二零一三年六月二十六日提交本會審覽嘅《二零一三年律師一般事務費修訂規則》嘅修訂期限，我請郭榮亨議員發言以及動議案。郭榮亨議員。
Thank you, President.
In my capacity as the chairman of the subcommittee to study the Solicitors General Cost Amendment Rules 2013, gazetted on the 21st of June 2013 as LN 110 of 2013, I moved a motion standing in my name on the agenda, as LN 1110 were not.
由成本委員會，作為根據《律師業條例》第74條所規定，該委員會認為《L.N.110》無效，並無任何法律效力。根據行政局的説法，成本委員會將盡力制定一套新的
新修訂條文，與一個議程，解釋背後的原因，需要制定新條文，以及犯錯的社會法律委員會。然而，由於L N一百一十已經刊憲，該小組仍須找出處理及解決現況的方法。
There are several legal options presented to members of the subcommittee on how to deal with and resolve the current situation, and there are constitutional implications arising from the same. Members do not wish to set a wrong precedent if similar incidents are to take place in the future.
Members of the subcommittee have different views on how the matter should be resolved, due to differences of opinion, on the matter, and to allow members more time and opportunity to review and study the different views of the subcommittee, which will be fully contained and set out in its report to this council. I now move a motion.
要延長審查期的L.N.110至議會會議，於11月6日2013年。
The motion is now moved. Thank you, President.
現場嗰啲提出嘅代議議題係郭榮亨議員動議嘅議案，二二通過，有冇議員要發言？
我現在我喺提出上述代決議題，付諸表決。
贊成嘅請舉手。
反對嘅請舉手。我認為議題獲得經由功能團體選舉產生及分區直接選舉產生兩部分在席議員分別以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。